# V V S KRISHNA TEJA

• Marketing Specialist & Content Writer •

#### ABOUT ME

I've always believed careers are laid on the foundation of inquisitiveness and built with experience. Being someone who enjoys learning, I bring to the table, the experience of building a start-up, the know-how of scaling businesses, and studying markets, both via books and hands-on experience in the Digital Marketing and Content Writing domain.

#### EXPERIENCE

# Khairah Group of Companies

# Marketing Partner (March 2021 - July 2021)

- Efficiently translated the respective business vision, direction, and goals of three companies, namely DestinationOne Consulting, Tecie and CanMar Group into SEO-friendly blogs, Social media content, Talk shows, Podcasts and webinars.
- Developed, launched, and brought to life at every touchpoint the brands and image for the company through content marketing.
- Offered alternatives as to how the content, design, and functionality of the website/platform can be improved & achieved 25% month-on-month growth.

## **ZOHO Corporation Pvt Ltd**

## Content Writer (October 2020 - March 2021)

- Writing content for new and updated product features, error messages and inapp notifications.
- Ideate on topics, and publish B2B blogs for product launches, announcements and feature releases.
- Creating knowledge base articles, writing help documents and support the social media team with executing content calendar for Twitter.

#### Pickyourtrail

# Assistant Sales Manager - (November 2019 - September 2020)

- Authoring blogs at <u>pickyourtrail.com/blog</u>.
- Working across various functions which Include Content Marketing, SEO Writing, and B2B Partnerships.
- Copywriting for Campaigns, projects, and initiatives. Backlinking, Keyword research, Rank analysis for existing blogs.
- Have led a team of 12 in planning and executing media-focused promotions for a Sale Campaign whilst achieving Revenue targets.

# Woovly India Pvt Ltd

## Management Trainee - (April 2019 - October 2019)

- Analyzing, defining, and categorizing the market into strata. Identifying potential merchants and business partners, to take the brand to users through various marketing channels.
- Single-handedly onboarded over 300 merchant profiles onto the platform via Email marketing, Cold-calling.
- Communicating, negotiating, and cutting deals with both the Merchants and the opinion leaders for revenue generation.
- Developing strategies, creating product workflows and business presentations, to cater to different stakeholders of the business; the users, the vendors, and potential brand ambassadors.

## EDUCATION

# SKILLS

2017 - 2019 • M.B.A • 70%

AMRITA SCHOOL OF BUSINESS
Coimbatore

Campaign Management

2013 - 2016 • B.COM • 86%

Wordpress

ANDHRA UNIVERSITY Visakhapatnam

#### CERTIFICATIONS

Google analytics academy

#### HOBBIES

Social Media operations

Marketing Tools: Digital Marketing
LinkedIn Learning
Content Marketing Certified
Hubspot learning
Certified Inbound Marketing
Hubspot learning
Google Analytics for Beginners

Photography

Gaming

Travel

Gardening